{
    "decks": [
        {
            "title": "Korean Vocabulary (People)",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "front": "아기",
                    "back": "Baby"
                },
                {
                    "front": "아이",
                    "back": "Child"
                },
                {
                    "front": "학생",
                    "back": "Student"
                },
                {
                    "front": "아버지",
                    "back": "Father"
                },
                {
                    "front": "아빠",
                    "back": "Dad"
                },
                {
                    "front": "어머니",
                    "back": "Mother"
                },
                {
                    "front": "암마",
                    "back": "Mum"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Korean Vocabulary (Food)",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "front": "오이",
                    "back": "Cucumber"
                },
                {
                    "front": "우유",
                    "back": "Milk"
                },
                {
                    "front": "맛",
                    "back": "Flavour, the flavour, taste"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Korean Vocabulary (Animals)",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "front": "닭",
                    "back": "Chicken"
                },
                {
                    "front": "여우",
                    "back": "Fox"
                },
                {
                    "front": "개미",
                    "back": "Ant"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Korean Vocabulary (Example Sentences)",
            "cards": [
                {
                    "front": "이것은 아기의 우유 입니다.",
                    "back": "This is baby's milk."
                },
                {
                    "front": "이것은 아기의 젖이다.",
                    "back": "This is baby's milk."
                },
                {
                    "front": "이 학생의 신문.",
                    "back": "This student's newspaper."
                },
                {
                    "front": "이 아이의 요요.",
                    "back": "This is the child's yoyo."
                },
                {
                    "front": "이 노래의 메시지.",
                    "back": "This song's message."
                },
                {
                    "front": "학생용 열쇠.",
                    "back": "A student's key."
                },
                {
                    "front": "어, 이건 아기의 우유야.",
                    "back": "Oh, this is the baby's milk."
                },
                {
                    "front": "한국의 신문.",
                    "back": "Newspapers in Korea, Korean Newspapers"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
